Guide to the Stanford University, Planning Office, Records SC0486
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2008-194
  - Science and Engineering Quad 2-Robert A.M. Stern Architects, 6/2/2004 (Box 5)
  - Sand Hill Road Hotel & Office Development, 7/15/2005 (Box 5)
  - Stanford Graduate School of Business Knight Management Center Proposal- William Rawn Associates, Architects, Inc. (Box 5)
  - Stanford Graduate School of Business Knight Management Center Proposal-Bohlin Cywinski Jackson (Box 5)
  - Stanford Graduate School of Business Knight Management Center Proposal-Polshek Partnership Architects (Box 5)
  - Near West Campus Redevelopment Project/A.M.R. Building (Box 6)
  - Stanford University-GSB Residential Learning Center (Box 6)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research-Schematic Design Report, 8/28/1996 (Box 6)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research-Stanford University School of Medicine-Design Development Report, 2/21/1997 (Box 6)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research-Stanford University School of Medicine-Design Development Report, 7/1997 (Box 6)
  - Stanford Law School Master Plan Report, 9/2001 (Box 6)
  - Rosco Maples Pavilion: Improvements Concept Report, 1/2002 (Box 7)
  - Escondido Housing Feasibility Study Stanford University, 7/2000 (Box 7)
  - Alumni Center. SWA Group. Landscape design., undated (Box 8)
  - Papua New Guinea Sculpture Garden. Tom Richman & Associates. 2 Mounted drawings., undated (Box 8)
  - Maples Pavilion Improvement Study. HOK Sport. Spiral bound booklet., undated (Box 8)
  - Stanford Band Facility. Eve Siu-Tracy., 2001 Apr (Box 8)
  - Law School Improvements. Skimmer, Owings & Merrill. 19 page packet of drawings., 1996 (Box 8)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2008-253
  - Design guidelines - drafts, responses, letters, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - GPI projects (mostly as overhead slides), 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2010-050
  - Campus Drive Design Guidelines 2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching - information brochure 1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Casper, Gerhard - statement on faculty housing, March 4, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Land Use Planning Presentation to the Board of Trustees, Dec. 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Menlo Park Urban Design Plans 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous memos 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Notes of Mr. Spencer's speech before Pacific Coast Association of Physical Plant Administrators of Universities and Colleges, Dec. 4, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Palo Alto, correspondence with or about, 1980-2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Portola Valley, correspondence with or about, 1993-94 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Research Park Study, April 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Santa Clara County, correspondence with or about, 1985-92 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Stanford architectural plans, 1982-85 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Vegetation management plan, 1982-96 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2015-019
  - Specifications for Remodeling of Main Library Building, Leland Stanford Jr. University, 1970 May 19 (Box 1)
  - Specifications for General Construction of Undergraduate Library, Leland Stanford Jr. University, 1964 Aug 1 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Main Library Development, Construction Specifications Not for Construction, 1976 Sep 27 (Box 1)
  - Specifications for Main Library Development, New Building, Leland Stanford Jr. University, 1970 Dec 10 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Main Library Development, 1975 Nov 14 (Box 1)
  - Contract Documents and Specifications, Library Quad Transverse (1088), Stanford University, 1978 May (Box 1)
  - Specifications for Main Library Development, New Building, Leland Stanford Jr. University, 1970 Jun 15 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Main Library Development, Construction Specifications Not for Construction, 1976 Oct 5 (Box 1)
  - Computer Sciences Building, Stanford University, Schematic Design Stage, 1969 Feb 20 (Box 1)
  - Project Manual, Mathematical Sciences Library, Remodeling and Renovation, Stanford University, 1978 Feb 22 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Main Library, Cecil H. Green Remodeling, Design Development Cost Estimate, 1979 Jun 1 (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous Drawings and Maps, 1960-1993; Accession 2010-146; 1 Linear Feet
  - Stanford University Medical Center Site and Floor Plans, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Street Numbering Map (residential areas), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Professional - Administrative - Commercial Center Map, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Industrial Park Map, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Shopping Center Map (some businesses identified), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Quad and Building Numbers Map, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lands of Leland Stanford Junior University Map, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Tour Maps (for Trustees, County Supervisors), 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Drawing of an unidentified building (pen and pastel) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Printing films, with some printed examples, for a Medical Center publication, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Additional Material, ARCH-2017-027
  - "Stanford University: SEQ 2 Master Plan and Guidelines," boora/Hargreaves/Arup, 2005 (Box 1)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2017-028
  - "Report of Archaeological Findings at CA-SCL-613, Children's Health Council Santa Clara County, California: Prepared for compliance with City of Palo Alto Use Permit 94-UP-21 and Mitigated Negative Declaration 94-EIA-13," Prepared with Laura Jones, Ph.D; Eva Bunker, B.A.; Elizabeth Burson, B.A.; Marco De Masi, M.A.; Karen Gust, B.A.; Julia Hammett, Ph.D.; Frances Hayashida, Ph.D.; Elena Reese, M.A., and Susanne Rodriguez, 1997 Jun 4 (Box 1)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2017-123
  - Science and Engineering Quad 2 Master Plan, 2004-4-19 (Box 1)
  - The Clark Center: Scheme V, 2000-6-6 (Box 1)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2018-041
  - Charles Coolidge, "Random Jottings" (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Main Quad - Outer Court Graphics (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Demolished Buildings, circa 2000s (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Schwab Residential Center, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Anderson Stucco, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - HEPL, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)